

PROFILE

A multilingual; first it was Spanish to speak to most of the western hemisphere, then it was code to speak to computers. I use it to create, and can't wait to apply it to amazing experiences, groundbreaking services, and revolutionary ideas.

TECHNOLOGIES

Languages:HTML, CSS, JavaScriptFront End:Angular, Ionic, ReactBack End:Node, Express, Mongo

Deploy/Host: Firebase, Heroku, Netlify

Versioning: Git, Github **CMS:** WordPress

Design: Adobe XD, Inkscape

EDUCATION

Softstack Factory

Fullstack Certification, 2018

Western Washington University

BA - Spanish, 2018

AUSTIN WIESE FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

- i awstin17.github.io/portfolio
- 360-593-9466
- austinwiese.acw@gmail.com
- in /austinwiese-acw
- github.com/awstin17

WORK EXPERIENCE

MiCastr, Web App Prototyper

MAR 2019 - CURRENT

- Turned sketches and ideas into clickable prototype with Adobe XD
- Established UI needs and aesthetic with client
- Currrently coding full stack demo based on mockup

Flying Penguin PR, WordPress Web Designer

FEB 2019 - FEB 2019

- Fixed display bugs under an urgent deadline
- Used custom CSS to make website responsive
- Resolved spam issue that sparked site overhaul

What's In The Bags, WordPress Internship

NOV 2018 - FEB 2019

- Debugged by cooperating with hosting provider's customer service
- Designed logo with Inkscape and site mockup with Adobe XD
- Tested and iterated subscription feature until it was flawless

PROJECTS

InTransition App - (Used: MongoDB, Express, Node, Ionic)

Demo: https://reboot-demo-2.firebaseapp.com/

- An Ionic iPad app meant to help veterans transition to civilian life
- Developed in team of 5 in agile workflow
- Created dashboard view, charts to display data from backend

Stockathon App - (Used: MongoDB, Express, Node, Angular)

Demo: https://stockathon.netlify.com/

- An Angular app to help you track stock data
- Created REST API with Node to create and store user data
- Made requests to Alpha Vantage API to retrieve stock data